这个问题的答案是ListPreference.当设置
The solution to this question is ListPreference. When the setting
被点击后，一列选择被展示出来作为
is tapped, it presents a list of choices as a
一个对话框，当用户选择一个选项，它被保存进入
dialogue. When a user selects an option, it's saved into
SharedPreferences。这是做这件事的步骤：在
SharedPreferences. Here are the steps to do this. Within
pref_general.xml这个文件里我们加入一个ListPreference。我们给
the pref_general.xml file we add a list preference. We give
它设置一个title(标题），这与气温单位匹配。
it a title, and this maps to the string temperature
我们还需要给它一个key(键)用于
units. We also need to give it a key for
SharedPreferences。然后我们把key定义为units。
the SharedPreferences. And so we specify that to be units.
如果SharedPreferences中没有值，它将会
If there is no value in SharedPreferences, then it
使用默认值：公制单位。这个Preference
falls back to a default value of metric. The preference
也需要知道所有可能的值。
also wants to know the list of all possible values
我们现在有两个可能的值：公制单位或英制单位。所以我们
here. The two possible values are metric or imperial. So we
把他们以数组的形式传递给entryValues。现在
pass those in as an array, into entry values. Now
这些仅仅是常量 用于程序的逻辑中
these are just constants for use within the logic of our
并非用户可见的字符串。所以我们
app, these are not the user visible strings. So we
需要创建用户可见的选项 它是一个用户可见字符串的数组
need to create entries which is an array of user visible
这个数组将每一个可能的值都加在里面
strings that maps to each one of these possible values. To
为了使气温单位选项在SettingsActivity里显示
have the temperature unit preference show up in the settings activity,
我们在onCreate方法中进行修改。我们添加这一行
we modify the on create method. We add this line of
代码在气温单位设定里。当用户在对话框中
code for the temperature units setting. When the user makes a
做出一个选择，我们给PreferenceSummary设置
selection in the dialog, we set the preference summary to be
一个新的值：公制或英制。这里，当我们
the new value of either metric or imperial. Here, when we
得到一个最高气温一个最低气温，我们从SharedPreferences中
receive a high and low temperature, we read from SharedPreferences
得知气温是否要被转成英制或者
to know whether the temperature should be converted to imperial units or
直接保留为公制。然后我们将特定格式的字符串返回用以显示在
left as metric. Then we return the formatted string for display in
用户界面。保存天气单位设定的代码完成。
the UI. That completes the code for saving the temperature unit setting.